Hey everyone, today's video will be on
how to make insurance for JCB on the
ICA portal. So, first of all, we will see
what a JCB is. For
those who do not know what a JCB is,
you see, the crane type
and the construction equipment, that is,
we count them in construction equipment
and we
count it under the miscellaneous category like
goods carrier, two wheeler, four wheeler,
passenger carrying vehicle, similarly,
these tractors, JCBs and one or two
more vehicles which are construction equipment,
we count them in ICA. So,
you can see on the screen
what a JCB is and what the look of a JCB is like.
So now
we will learn to make its insurance. Come, it is a
common thing on the portal, we
will click on the motor because we are
making insurance for the motor. Click on the motor.
As soon as you click on the motor, an
arrow is shown. Click on the arrow on the left side. As soon as you click on the arrow, the
option of miscellaneous equipment appears. Package policy, this is us.
I am teaching you how to make JCB insurance.
Click on the package from the new JCB new invoice. Then after clicking on the package, we have to
enter the details. We have to
fill in the details. The RTO location of the registration
office is
in which city it is registered. This will be available, so
you enter the RTO location here. Then
we have added Sonipat and
selected it from the details of the vehicle.
First registration date which is today's date will
remain the same. Individual company name,
partnership name, company name is on this and
check the policy start date. Year of
manufacture is 2024. Is the policy type normal
or short term? So normal one year
insurance. Click on vehicle details.
Manufacturer. First of all,
we will enter the manufacturer. Mahindra. Now I am
telling you that this is Mahindra Earth Master
JCB, so
we will select Mahindra Construction Equipment
because this is construction equipment and its
Earth Master model is Earth Master.
We have selected that. Then we will enter the sub class
back.  He has picked up the order, seating
capacity is one cubic capacity is one body
type is open diesel fuel type and then now we will give you
change of 5 by 5 from the invoice
so where there is change showroom price,
enter the invoice price which I have
30 lakhs 30 lakhs, if I am entering then
in change of ID, according to you, by 5 by 5,
it will take 285000, sorry, it will take
850000, we do
not need to add it by 5, it will automatically
switch these details, then
click submit, policy class public
type vehicle usage construction is
used in construction, this vehicle is used in
construction, then area of ​​destination national
national permit is there, then instead of
vehicle owner driver owner driver
national you can also click on construction site
owner
driver then buy now and we have an option
click here to customize cover click here cover will
click it will not cover
because it will not cover the firm
name because only driver and  75%
discount is the highest mentioned in ICI
and if there is an OD discount then
we will add 75% discount to it. We have to
add three covers IT 23 PA
Driver PA. We add the cover when it is on
individual name. Otherwise 75%
discount liability to pay driver will
click on one and IMT 23 cover and will recalculate it. As soon as it is
recalculated,
scroll up and you will get the
premium ₹20000 ₹10. This is our premium. Then
we can also check it by breaking up the new premium. Check all the details.
Which IDV covers have been added and
how much premium has been made.
You can check all these details here.
See, IT 23 cover has been added and
pay driver has also been added, discount has also been added
and 280000 IDV will go back to the
plan. Click on buy now. As soon as you
click on buy now, Engine Chase will
ask for it. Same age invoice has to be entered now.  I am
entering random details. You have to
enter the exact engine change number and
vehicle colour. You should enter it according to your details.
Loan. If it is a financed vehicle, then
mention it by clicking on loan and hypothecation. Now I will mention and show it.
What is the financial name?
Corporation GST number or GST
certificate. We will enter the document according to that.
We will submit the details and then we are
submitting the details. If we are
not able to fetch the details, then we will
try with the PAN number. Here we will
remove the last three digits in the GST number itself and remove the first two digits. Then
this will become our PAN number. We will enter the
date of incorporation and submit.
Something is not coming in colour.
Click again on complete KYC. Then
here you upload the photo of GST certificate or PAN
card. As soon as you
upload the photo, it will
fetch all the details.
Uploading the photo is a better choice
here because it has address and  Everything according to you,
click on submit, it will
pick up all the details according to you,
so as soon as you click on submit, you will see that the
processing is going on on your screen, then
thank you, your document is submitted
for manual QC process, please
click on the OK button, then
here you can manually enter the details,
customer name or the name of your firm
like Sir Makers or Balaji Motors
or Builders, whatever the name is, enter it,
enter the date of incorporation and
enter the address, right now I will enter a random address,
enter the pin code, you have picked the
state and city according to your location,
it has picked up the mobile number and email
ID, so you can also enter the email ID, then
if you want to enter the PIN number, you can enter it,
click on create proposal, then an error is showing, it is
showing an error, it is showing an error because
we have entered the email in the alternate email, so
because of this it is showing an error, so we
will cut the mail from here and then we will
copy it in the email, then error  It will not be shown,
click on Create Proposal, as soon as you
click on Create Proposal,
our proposal has been successfully created,
click on Buy Now, then
you can check all the details
and click on Send Link, this is the
email ID and number on which you want to send the link,
you can share it, this is the
method to make JCB insurance, thank you so much